<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Kim Haroche</title>
    <link>https://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Kim Haroche</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© Untitled. All rights reserved</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://example.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/about/</guid>
      <description>Who I Am I am a registered psychotherapist, counselor, and skilled practitioner trained in:&#xA;Trauma resolution Nervous system regulation Mindfulness meditation Attachment issues Grief counseling Sensorimotor Psychotherapy Biodynamic Cranial Sacral Therapy Embryology (including working with babies and new mothers) Master Pilates Teacher, second generation. I have had the wonderfully enriching experiences of being a Teaching Assistant at the Colorado School of Energy Studies, and at the Sensorimotor Psychotherapy Institute, a Meditation instructor in international month-long silent meditation retreats, and a Trainer and Presenter of the Pilates Center Certification and Master’s Program.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Counseling Services</title>
      <link>https://example.org/counseling-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/counseling-services/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cranial Sacral Therapy</title>
      <link>https://example.org/cranio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/cranio/</guid>
      <description>For People “There are inherent, intelligent and unexplained forces that create and maintain the human body.” These forces, also known as the embryological formative forces, appear during conception and continue to shape us today. My job, through Biodynamic Cranial Sacral Therapy (BCST), is to listen to these forces with openness and presence; thereby allowing these dynamic forces to naturally come forth and reorganize your system to a new level of health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pilates</title>
      <link>https://example.org/pilates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/pilates/</guid>
      <description>Workshops Stillness in Motion—Cranial Sacral for Pilates teachers A New Approach to Pilates—Pilates and the Autonomic Nervous System Kathy Grant’s Early Work The Magic of Springs The Forgotten Exercises Mentoring Groups I am happy to offer mentoring groups and enjoy exploration of the method as a group. It is up to the client to arrange for a group workshop; we can meet live in Boulder, or at your studio, or via Zoom.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://example.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/contact/</guid>
      <description>Email: kimharoche@gmail.com&#xA;Mobile: +1.720.352.6669&#xA;WhatsApp: +1.720.352.6669&#xA;In-Person Sessions:&#xA;My office is located on 23rd and Pearl St in Boulder, CO.&#xA;Zoom Sessions:&#xA;A link will be sent once an appointment has been confirmed.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
